Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
-Set up a 20-meter perimeter.
-Roger that.
Commander Berger. you know the procedure.
As of now. you're in custody.
Yeah.
ELITE FORCE
Sorry to keep you waiting.
I'm sure we'll resolve this quickly.
I'd just like to clarify a few details.
So. you left your phone
in the locker room?
Yes. I left my phone in the locker room.
It's unlike you to be unreachable.
It's also unlike me
to pay tribute to one of my partners.
Maybe my mind was elsewhere.
On the anniversary
of your former partner's death.
you went to the site where he died.
In the 15 years since his death.
have you ever made such a trip.
on that date. to that place?
No.
Why this year?
Maybe because of Christophe's death.
-I felt the need to.
-The need to pay your respects?
Yes.
Armed with an AK-47 assault rifle
and a Kel-Tec shotgun.
I'm the cautious type.
Looks like I was right to be.
I'm cautious too.
But I don't bring a whole arsenal
to my father's grave.
Maybe the difference between us
lies in how dangerous our jobs are.
Have you or your father ever been targeted
by a car bomb at work?
Have you and your father.
in the course of your work.
ever wondered
if you were going to make it home alive
to kiss your family goodnight?
Maybe if your job
was a little more dangerous
than just handing out red cards
to people doing theirs…
perhaps you'd see things differently.
My father was a general
in the French Armed Forces.
But I understand what you're saying.
What's strange is that
these weapons aren't registered anywhere.
No permits were ever issued.
They're ghost guns.
These weapons were seized
on a recent mission.
I followed protocol to register them.
I guess the paperwork got lost somewhere
in the maze of red tape.
Mea culpa.
Fine me.
Please.
90 rounds of 7.62 mm ammo for the AK-47
and 30 Brenneke rounds for the shotgun.
I'm confused. Commander.
Is that standard ammunition
for these weapons?
We choose ammunition
based on our missions.
You'd know that if you had
the slightest interest in our jobs.
So. what kind of mission
requires Brenneke rounds?
The kind requiring heavy firepower.
So. armed with an assault rifle
and a shotgun.
both unregistered
and therefore untraceable.
with ammo chosen for maximum power.
you drove to the site
where your partner died.
illegally entering a military facility.
something you'd never done in 15 years.
And then. by some tragic coincidence.
you ran into Mayard.
the sole suspect in your boss' death.
You arrested him.
and despite your expertise
and your extensive experience
within the GIGN.
he managed to grab a weapon
and you shot him. Is that correct?
Minus the sarcasm. yes.
I promised that if you crossed the line
one more time. I'd ensure it was the last.
I will keep my promise.
I can assure you.
Yes.
Mrs. Berger. come in.
A police report. filed by
one of your daughter's classmates.
regarding events that occurred
during a party at his home.
He describes an altercation
between Manon Berger's father
and several of his guests.
If it were serious. the prosecutor
would've taken it up and filed charges.
This is just a police report.
Indeed. Pressured by his father.
the young man withdrew his statement.
blaming it on the alcohol.
The prosecutor was therefore
unable to take up the case.
So? That doesn't explain why I'm here.
Your husband is trained in violence.
He's an expert in every form of combat.
In short. he's a weapon.
At 1:00 a.m.. your daughter
wasn't answering her phone.
He panicked. When he found her…
he tasered the guy.
I have to wonder. Mrs. Berger.
When his loved ones are involved.
just how far will your husband go?
David's job is to protect.
You. me. his daughter. everyone.
His mission comes first. Always.
It's called a work ethic.
Does the premeditated killing of a suspect
fall under what you call a work ethic?
How long have you been working
with Commander Berger?
Five years.
A little longer.
How would you describe his leadership?
Exemplary.
Would you say
you're close to Commander Berger?
You know. the GIGN is one big family.
We're all brothers in arms.
There's no sound on this video.
but do you remember what you said
to the Commander at that moment?
Not really. no. The usual. I guess.
Upcoming training. how our kids are doing.
The bag looks particularly heavy.
Do you have any idea what was in it?
He left the armory with a bag.
You know very well what's in it.
Why are you asking me?
There was no target practice scheduled
and no operations that day.
Why take weapons out?
We're elite marksmen.
we take weapons in and out all the time.
Nothing surprising there.
Yet you look surprised in this footage.
That's your interpretation.
I think you knew the commander
wasn't going to training.
I think you warned him.
You're an honest man.
And because you're loyal.
you're keeping quiet today.
But loyal to whom? That's the question
you need to ask yourself.
To your men?
Or to your friend?
Do you think driving in the dead of night
to an abandoned military base.
running into the suspect by chance.
heavily armed. then shooting him.
is the behavior
of a responsible GIGN leader?
The commander made a choice.
He chose personal revenge
at the expense of the entire GIGN.
Not to mention the missing CL20 stock.
We have no chance of ever finding it
now that the main suspect is dead.
Now you. Major?
What choice will you make?
During the Kröller op.
when we were attacked
by the sniper in the woods…
I'm not sure what.
But he brought something back.
Where were you last night?
I was at home. Alone. in my apartment.
You weren't at home.
You were there when he shot Mayard.
You deliberately concealed your presence.
You know what that means.
Your career is over.
Do you know what this is?
SEALED - DO NOT OPEN
It looks like a cartridge case
used by the sniper
who shot the arms dealer.
Kröller.
It was in your home.
Can you explain why it was there?
You know. long-range shooting
is one of my specialties.
I've accumulated a lot of casings
over the years.
Why do you think
we went as far as searching your home?
Tenacity.
Major Bonenfant. your colleague.
Your friend. even. Cédric.
He told me about it.
You are aware that removing evidence
from a crime scene
is grounds for court-martial.
Another coincidence?
Like the weapons you took from the armory.
Like being in the right place
at the right time to shoot the terrorist.
I have another explanation.
As you might've guessed.
On graduation night. Christophe.
your superior. your mentor. the man
who taught you everything. is killed.
Your world collapses.
You start your own parallel investigation.
You illegally interrogate a suspect
you just arrested.
You take evidence from a crime scene.
You track down Mayard.
but he slips away at the hospital.
So. you go through
your Intel colleague's computer.
You finally get a lead on the suspect.
Your rogue investigation
becomes a revenge mission.
Commander. may I speak with you?
After every shot.
my men are detained. It's procedure.
The police handle it.
I don't get involved.
Now I find out that you. the IGGN.
have been interrogating my men
since this morning?
You even summoned David's wife?
So I need to know
if you're just being overzealous
or if I should be worried.
Come with me.
The SD card from your vehicle's dashcam
has mysteriously disappeared.
Another coincidence.
Luckily. the dashcams were just updated.
I triggered the recording remotely.
The footage went straight to the server.
Villiers?
David.
The question now is
whether you'll go to prison or not.
When did you decide to kill Mayard?
What role did your mentee play
in your plans?
Can I ask you to stop recording?
And can Spielberg leave?
I'll confess everything.
The murder. the premeditation. everything.
But on two conditions.
First. Max stays out of this.
He followed me. not knowing what I'd do.
I forced him to stay quiet.
He's not involved.
Second.
let me go home tonight.
To see my family.
And I'll confess tomorrow.
Even when you've lost. you try to bend
the rules to your advantage.
Why would I agree to that?
Why wouldn't you agree to that?
Right now. all you have is a lie
about Max's involvement in this.
And a few minor offenses. Nothing much.
It's enough to have you and Max
dismissed from the force.
Yeah.
But what would really make you happy?
A mere dismissal?
Or the chance to put me behind bars?
-You good? Not too much adrenaline?
-We're all good.
-Hey.
-How's it going?
Hi.
Here we go again. guys.
Move out. let's go.
Come on. bring it down! Keep going!
Quick. let's go inside.
Come on!
It's in! Let's go!
Police!
Too slow. guys.
Within ten seconds. they could be dead.
Come on. let's go. Take a right.
Go right!
Move forward!
Okay. stop.
Guys. debrief in ten minutes.
Change and meet me at the command post.
We're all behind you. okay?
You okay. man?
Hey. asshole.
If you want to talk. I'm here. okay?
I probably would've done the same.
Where were you?
I didn't come here to talk.
Since when does the IGGN
interrogate wives?
She's an overzealous commander.
She thinks you executed the guy
who killed Christophe.
Custody is 24 hours.
Why did she let you out?
Because I confessed.
What?
I made a deal with her.
I'll sign whatever she wants tomorrow.
In return. she's letting me
spend the evening with you.
The evening?
What are you saying?
Did you kill him or not?
I could have.
What the fuck are you doing?
You'll end up in prison.
Max is involved in this. isn't he?
You don't owe him anything.
What about Manon?
Do you think I'm happy about this?
Do you think it's easy for me?
I have to do this.
For Max. I have to do this.
It's pointless being here tonight
if you won't be tomorrow.
Pointless.
You're leaving?
It was nice. I have to go.
Wait. You can't just show up at my door
and not explain anything to me.
I don't want to talk about it.
It's about David. isn't it?
Killing the terrorist.
He emptied out his locker.
I heard he got fired.
David didn't shoot.
I did.
Wait. what?
What are you talking about?
I was with David. I followed him.
We arrested the terrorist together.
It went wrong.
I screwed up.
So why is David being fired
if you're the one who shot the gun?
He told the IGGN that he was alone.
That I wasn't there.
He's taking the fall for me.
You're letting him?
He's lied to me from the start.
Before Mayard died. he said
David was to blame for my dad's death.
Does that justify him taking the fall?
He deserves to be punished.
Yeah. he does.
But not like this.
-I'm going to tell her the truth.
-Don't. Look at me.
If you do. your career is over.
My career is behind me.
It's…
About my dad. Mayard says it's your fault.
You say it's not.
You're ready to ruin your life for me.
A month ago. you forgot I even existed.
Max…
It must be because you feel guilty.
Explain why you're risking it all.
or I'll walk in there
and tell them the truth.
Lone terrorist.
Former lab staff. idealistic type.
He wants all of France to see
the weapons they're designing here.
All I know is that it's explosives.
Same partners as usual.
Usual rules of engagement.
Self-defense. hostage in danger.
or a direct order.
Okay. everyone? Let's go.
All right. let's go. guys.
Christophe. I want to change partners.
On what grounds?
It's for the best.
You two. I don't know what the issue is.
but I'll be brief.
There's a terrorist
and 21 hostages who need us.
Don't make me regret
having you in this section. Do your job.
Okay.
My daughter.
Evacuate!
Doc! Over here!
I'm a dad too. ma'am. I'm a dad too.
I'll go get your daughter.
My daughter is in the lab!
-Everybody. we're evacuating!
-No. wait!
This way!
We need to be out of here in 50 seconds.
Lina!
Everyone. evacuate!
-Lina. we're with your parents!
-David. Laurent! Get out of there.
-Lina!
-Initiating emergency procedure.
-Do you copy? Get out of there now!
Lina. if you're hiding.
you need to come out!
-David.
-Lina!
-I can't wait any longer.
Laurent. we need to leave. damn it.
We need to get out of here!
It's an order! Out!
-We have to go.
-We won't leave until we find her. Lina!
-We need to fucking leave!
-Lina!
-Come on.
-Let go of me. damn it!
Get your hands off me!
She's not here. It's about to blow up.
We need to go.
Get out of here then!
Fuck!
David. Look at me.
Get out. David.
-There has to be another way out.
-It's over.
We both know it. Get out of here. please.
Please.
I'm sorry. Laurent.
I'm sorry.
Take care of Max for me.
Go on. get out.
Get out of here!
I knew you were still here.
My name is Laurent.
Will you come with me?
It's going to be okay.
Is Mommy coming to get me?
Yes. she is.
There's one thing I don't get.
If you're not to blame for his death.
why do all this for me?
Because it's still kind of my fault.
I mean. the fact that
Laurent was so angry that day
was partly my fault.
He'd just received some test results.
He found out he couldn't have children.
That he never could.
I kept it secret all these years
at your mother's request. but…
I couldn't do it anymore.
I am your father.
Listen.
I know I haven't been there for you
since Laurent died. I…
Your mother wanted me to stay away.
and I get that.
Maybe I was an idiot for listening to her.
I don't know.
I can't go back in time.
I can't change the past.
But there is something I can do now.
For you.
I can protect you now.
Major Villiers?
We weren't expecting you.
I need to talk to you.
Come in.
I'll tell you what really happened.
Give me five minutes.
Hi. sweetheart. How are you?
You lied to me.
What do you mean?
About Dad. About David.
How could you do that?
Wait. Where are you?
Let's talk about it. okay?
No.
Tell me where you are.
Max.
Max. please. tell me where you are.
Max?
Gentlemen. ready to come back in?
Shit.
I have rarely seen so many breaches
of procedure. GIGN ethics. and the law.
You played vigilante.
tried to arrest him. and he died.
Granted. it was self-defense. but he died.
If I had my way. you'd be convicted.
A suspended sentence at the very least.
And probably prison time.
But it seems
it would serve no one's interests.
neither the GIGN's. nor the gendarmerie's.
for the two heroic officers
who stopped a bomber's deadly rampage
to be publicly sanctioned.
-Isn't that right. General?
-Yes.
That said. your actions have no place
in the gendarmerie. let alone the GIGN.
Commander. I expected better from you.
You dragged a young recruit
into a clandestine operation.
You're suspended pending early retirement.
You won't set foot in the barracks again.
Major Villiers. your inexperience
does not excuse your poor judgment.
The board will decide your fate
within two weeks.
Until then.
you may not participate in operations
or in training
without your section leader's approval.
The 500 kilos of explosives
are still out there.
I don't know what outcome will be.
but I'll be blunt.
You do not belong at the GIGN.
You're dismissed.
Max!
What else do you want to say?
I gave everything to be part of the GIGN.
All I wanted was to be like you and Dad!
But all that is bullshit!
You're not heroes! It's bullshit!
My love. do you know
where Daddy's office is?
Go there. hide. and don't make a sound.
Don't come out until you hear my voice.
Do you understand?
I'll come get you. I promise.
What about you?
Don't worry. you know us.
We're strong. We'll fight. We'll win.
When I say "run." you go.
Do you understand? I'll come get you.
Alright. go. sweetie.
Run.
-Go on.
-Go. Run!
Keep calm.
You! Get up! Now!
Goddammit!
Fuck!
Police!
Stay with me.
I'm a dad too. ma'am.
I'll go get your daughter.
Everyone. evacuate!
I'll come get you. I promise.
DANGER EXPLOSIVES
CL20
A HUMAN TRAGEDY AMID STATE SECRETS
NINE-YEAR-OLD LINA MAYARD
A LIFE CUT SHORT
Okay. You can sleep over at Nina's
on one condition. Practice your pieces.
And don't go out.
We're going to the conservatory.
then we'll go straight to Nina's.
-Bye. Mom. I love you.
-I love you too.
I've been suspended.
What?
I told Max everything.
I told him I was his father.
The idiot still decided to talk
to the inspector.
even though everything
was going to be just fine.
Going to prison to protect him
would've been just fine?
What would've been fine about that?
Jess. you know
I made a promise to Laurent.
Before he died.
I promised I'd take care of Max.
I promised him that I'd take care of Max.
I promised him.
COMMIT FOR LIFE
You really think
that's why you're doing all this?
That's bullshit.
Even if you hadn't promised.
you'd be doing the same thing.
Because the truth is. you feel so guilty.
You don't know what else to do
to stop blaming yourself.
When are you going to let yourself live?
When are you going to make time for us?
You're not guilty of anything.
I am guilty.
I'm guilty of betraying Laurent.
I'm guilty of putting him in that state
just before the op. I am.
I'm guilty of not being there for Max.
I wasn't there for him. for fuck's sake.
He's my son. I wasn't there for him.
And the truth is.
I'm not fucking there for you guys either.
I'm there for everyone else.
but my family always comes last.
I'm sorry.
Subtitle translation by: Alison Simpson
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm